1, 2 heat is on
Own it, burn it, kick it, flip that
3, 4 BABYMON
We gon' get this party started
Walk in, stomping like we own the place
Trust me, I'm not just a pretty face
Yeah, I know we're seven but we ate
We gon' get this party started
Know we got the style, we got the taste
Sweet and sour lemons, lemonade
Yeah, I know we're seven but we ate
Better run that, run that
Oh my, oh my, my 지금 이 순간
Oh my, oh my, my Let it hypnotize
Loosen up, watch me set the mood
Burn it up, do it like I do
Lose your mi-mi-mind Play the music Let's 춤
리듬을 삼켜 보자 춤
We turn it up, let's party
월, 화, 수, 목, 금, 토 모두 다 함께 취해 보자 춤
춤, 춤, 춤, 춤, 춤
We wanna ride this vibe
Get out the way like, Vroom, vroom
We only got tonight
You better dance like, 춤, 춤
Baby, check my style Check me out
Can't stop now Gotta keep it me like that
보여줄게 나의 춤, 춤, 춤
모두가 짹 소리 못하는 groove
I구역의 난 I'm a monster queen
Oh my, oh my, my 지금 이 순간
Burn it up, do it like I do
리듬을 삼켜 보자 춤